

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- 3D Studio Max / Mentalray (10 years)
- V-ray (5 years)
- Vectorworks (10 years)
- Sketchup (5 years)
- Adobe Creative Suite (10 years)
- HTML (1 year)
- CSS (1 year)
- Javascript (In Progress)
- Wordpress (3 years)

LET'S CHAT:

617-898-8070 16 Nelson Dr Apt 1A. Randolph, MA 02368

Linan.

htexhibitdesign@gmail.com

Portfolio:

huymtran.wixsite.com/htdesign/

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/huy-tran-1b309644

REFERENCES:

Available upon request

Huy M. Tran

Senior Exhibit Designer

HERE'S MY STORY

I'm an exhibit designer with more than 10 years of experience in the exhibit and trade show industry. Some people call it an environmental design; others call it a 3D design. I often describe my role as a brand promoter. Throughout my career, I use architectural design principles to promote brand experience through forms and spaces.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern Architect

ZGF ARCHITECTS LLP - PORTLAND, OR SUMMER 2007

- Create 3D models of buildings and furniture
- Assist architects with 3D rendering and visualization
- Create textures for use in 3D rendering

CAD Drafter

UNIVERSITY OF IDAHO - MOSCOW, ID 2008-2009

- Maintain and edit blueprints of various buildings on campus.
- Archive old blueprints

Teaching Assistant

UNIVERSITY OF IDAHO - MOSCOW, ID 2008-2009

- Critique second year design students' projects
- Give tutorials on Photoshop, Illustrator and 3D Studio Max

Senior Exhibit Designer

THE EXHIBIT SOURCE - WESTWOOD, MA 2010-PRESENT

- Develop concepts and prepare preliminary drawings of permanent and temporary exhibits, office interiors and environments
- Provide detailed construction drawings, material specifications and setup drawings.

EDUCATIONAL INFO

University of Idaho - Moscow, ID

M.ARCH MASTER IN ARCHITECTURE FOCUS ON MODULAR DESIGN

- Graduated Class of 2009 with a 4.0 GPA
- Winner of Juan & Sean De Leon Leadership Award
- Winner of Lloyd E. Stalker (Architecture Excellent Award)
- Winner of Hayes, Walter C. Engineering Scholarship

Manchester Christian Academy - Manchester, WA

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

- Graduated Class of 2004 Valedictorian